In Search of Tarzan with Jonathan Ross is a
documentary film directed by Luke Jeans.
A look at Tarzan on the big and small screen with
interviews with some of those who have played him.
Self, played by Jonathan Ross.
Self, played by Johnny Weissmuller Jr..
Self, played by Ron Ely.
Self, played by Ray Bradbury.
Self, played by Eve Brent.
Self, played by Bo Derek.
2025 in film is an overview of events, including award ceremonies, festivals, a list of
country- and genre-specific lists of films released, and notable deaths.
Shochiku and Gaumont celebrated their 130th anniversaries; 20th Century Studios and Republic Pictures
celebrated their 90th anniversaries; and Studio Ghibli celebrated its 40th anniversary.
Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer's first musical film The Broadway Melody (1929), known for being the first sound
film to win the Academy Award for Best Picture, entered the public domain this year.